<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Zack's Blog</title><link>https://zackhl.com/</link><description>Recent content on Zack's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 12:06:25 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://zackhl.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Memuat laman web atau blog peribadi anda secara percuma</title><link>https://zackhl.com/posts/malay-personal-website-tutorial/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 12:06:25 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://zackhl.com/posts/malay-personal-website-tutorial/</guid><description>Pengenalan Memiliki laman web peribadi atau laman web perniagaan tidak pernah begitu penting. Wabak Covid19 memaksa banyak orang menutup pintu perniagaan mereka kepada pengunjung fizikal dan mereka perlu beralih ke e-commerce dengan pantas (tengok 1, 2), sebahagian memilih platform yang sedia ada seperti Facebook, ataupun membayar syarikat pembangunan web. Bagi profesional yang baru menamatkan pengajian, bergelut dengan cara baru untuk menjadi relevan ketika pemohonan kerja dan ketika ditemuduga (tengok 3).</description></item><item><title>Create your own personal website or blog for free</title><link>https://zackhl.com/posts/personal-website-tutorial/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 12:06:25 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://zackhl.com/posts/personal-website-tutorial/</guid><description>Introduction Having a personal website or a business site has never been so important. Covid19 pandemic forced a lot of people to close the doors of their businesses to physical visitors and had to quickly transition to e-commerce (see 1, 2), some of them choosing existing platforms like Facebook, some others paying for web development companies. For newly graduated professionals struggled with a new way to be relevant when applying for jobs and being interviewed if remote scenarios (see 3).</description></item><item><title>Search Results</title><link>https://zackhl.com/search/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zackhl.com/search/</guid><description>This file exists solely to respond to /search URL with the related search layout template.
No content shown here is rendered, all content is based in the template layouts/page/search.html
Setting a very low sitemap priority will tell search engines this is not important content.
This implementation uses Fusejs, jquery and mark.js
Initial setup Search depends on additional output content type of JSON in config.toml ``` [outputs] home = [&amp;ldquo;HTML&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;JSON&amp;rdquo;] ```</description></item></channel></rss>